https://auchterlonies.com/content/6-privacy

Old CourseSalePre-Owned ClubsMens GolfClothingGiletGlovesHeadwearJacketScarfShirtsSweatersTopTrousersVestWindshirtWaterproof jacketWaterproof trouserFootwearShoesGolf clubsIronsPuttersDriverFairwayRescuePackage setsHybridPre-Owned ClubsLadies GolfClothingGiletHeadwearJacketShirtsSweatersTopTrousersWaterproof jacketFootwearShoesGift VouchersBrands
Call +44 (0) 1334 473253
Contact us
Create Account or Sign In
Search:
Call +44 (0) 1334 473253
Contact us
Create Account or Sign In
Basket
My Cart (0 Items) £ 0.00 No products
Free shipping!
Shipping
£ 0.00 Total
Check out
Product successfully added to your shopping cart
Quantity
Total
There are 0 items in your cart.
There is 1 item in your cart.
Total products (tax incl.)
Total shipping (tax excl.)
Free shipping!
Total (tax incl.)
Continue shopping
Proceed to checkout
Old CourseSalePre-Owned ClubsMens GolfClothingGiletGlovesHeadwearJacketScarfShirtsSweatersTopTrousersVestWindshirtWaterproof jacketWaterproof trouserFootwearShoesGolf clubsIronsPuttersDriverFairwayRescuePackage setsHybridPre-Owned ClubsLadies GolfClothingGiletHeadwearJacketShirtsSweatersTopTrousersWaterproof jacketFootwearShoesGift VouchersBrandsPrivacy StatementBob Millar Limited (T/A Auchterlonies of St Andrews) is committed to protecting your privacy. We believe that the lawful and correct treatment of personal data is critical to our successful operation, and to maintaining our customers' confidence in us. This Privacy & Data Protection Policy explains how we use the data which we collect about you, how you can instruct us if you prefer to limit the use of that data and procedures that we have in place to safeguard your privacy.
We ensure that all personal data collected and used by us is managed in accordance with the requirements of the Data Protection Act 1998 and the General Data Protection Regulation (EU 2016/679) (the “Data Protection Legislation”) and we recognise that, in order to maintain our reputation and integrity as an open and professional organisation, we must be fully compliant with this legislation. In order to ensure that your data is adequately protected, we review and audit how we handle personal data regularly. Furthermore, all staff handling your data are properly trained and understand that they are responsible for following the good practice set out in this Privacy & Data Protection Policy.Our PromiseIn accordance with the Data Protection Legislation, we will ensure that your data is:used fairly and lawfully and in a transparent manner;used only for specific, explicit and legitimate reasons;adequate,  relevant and not excessive having regard to the reason for which it is collected;accurate and up to date where possible; kept for no longer than necessary;used in line with your rights;kept secure;and transferred internationally only where necessary steps have been taken to ensure the adequate protection and security of the data.ConsentYou can visit our website (auchterlonies.com without disclosing any personally identifiable information about yourself.  However, in submitting any personal data to us, through or in connection with this website (including when you register), you signify your acknowledgment of our collection, use and disclosure of your personal data in accordance with this Privacy & Data Protection Policy.  We make all reasonable efforts to ensure that all information published on our website is accurate at the time of publication.
We reserve the right to make minor amends or modifications to this Privacy & Data Protection Policy from time to time, without notice to you, and if we do so, we will post the updated policy on our website.  It is your responsibility to check the Privacy & Data Protection Policy every time you submit information to us or place an order online.  Your continued use of our website after changes are posted constitutes your acceptance of the Privacy & Data Protection Policy, as modified by the posted changes.  If you do not agree with this Privacy & Data Protection Policy you must not submit information to us through or in connection with our website. If we make any major changes to this Privacy & Data Protection Policy which will affect your rights, we will notify you of this by email.
We assume no responsibility or liability for any information published on our website and we accept no liability for any claims, losses, demands or damages whatsoever in relation to any information, content, promotion, procedures, products or methods contained in or referred to in the material published on our website.  No exclusion is made, however, in respect of death or personal injury arising from our negligence.
You acknowledge that all telephone calls made to the company may be recorded for specific business purposes as permitted by the Telecommunications (Lawful Business Practice) (Interception of Communications) Regulations 2000.PurposeBob Millar Limited (T/A Auchterlonies of St Andrews) uses personal data held about you in the following ways: (i) to improve our website and to ensure that content from our website is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer or other access device; (ii) to improve service delivery; (iii) to contact you for the purposes of research and surveys; (iv)  to allow us to respond to your enquiries for further information and providing such information; (v) to administer our website and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, and testing purposes; (vi) to notify you about changes to our services; (vii) to allow us to consider your comments, queries and suggestions and respond, if necessary; (viii) as part of our efforts to keep our website safe and secure; (ix) to comply with any legal obligations; and (x) to enable or facilitate the exercise of our rights under our terms and conditions of website use.
Provided you have consented at the point of us collecting your personal data ,Bob Millar Limited (T/A Auchterlonies of St Andrews) also uses personal data to allow us to communicate with you by mail, telephone, fax, e-mail or other electronic messaging service (as a past or present customer), to advise you of recent news of the company, our work and the services we offer, future events and special offers available to you, which may be of interest to the discerning customer.  We may also collect personal data from time to time, to allow us to offer further opportunities which are available to you through our website, at your request.
You have the right to ask us not to process your personal information for marketing purposes. We will inform you (before collecting your information) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by contacting us at please e-mail us at sales@auchterlonies.com. You will also be given the opportunity to opt out of receiving marketing information on each piece of marketing information we send to you.   We may keep personal data which we collect for a reasonable period up to 3 years after you cease using the services on our website, for any of the purposes mentioned above.Your rights in relation to your dataWe aim to keep your personal data up to date and welcome any updates to your details or corrections to any inaccuracies.  You have the right to receive a copy of the personal data we hold about you and can ask the company to correct or update any inaccurate data. If you would like to receive a copy of this data, please let us know in writingUnsubscribeWhere processing of your personal data is based on your consent, you have the right to withdraw that consent at any time. If you no longer wish to subscribe to receive e-mails from us, either click the 'Unsubscribe' button, which appears on any e-mail sent by us (excluding e-mails sent that relate to an ongoing transaction). Alternatively, please e-mail info@auchterlonies.com and we shall remove your name from our subscriber list. To help our administrative staff, please type the words "Data Protection" as the subject of your e-mail.
You should note that such withdrawal of consent shall not affect any processing of your personal data which took place prior to the date of withdrawal, where valid consent was in place at the time of processing.Sharing personal data with third partiesBob Millar Limited (T/A Auchterlonies of St Andrews) does not pass data on to organisations/individuals who administer services on our behalf, including research and evaluation. We will never disclose your personal data to any entity with whom we do not have a working relationship. Owing to the global nature of the Internet infrastructure, the data you provide may be transferred in transit to countries outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). Any sharing of your personal data with third parties shall be in accordance with this Privacy & Data Protection Policy and with the Data Protection Legislation.
Countries outside the EEA may not have similar protections in place regarding your data and its use as set out in this Privacy & Data Protection Policy. However, all organisations/individuals employed to do this are contracted to comply with the standards of the Data Protection Legislation.PasswordsWhere you have been provided with (or where you have chosen) a password which allows you to access certain parts of the website, you are responsible for keeping the password safe and confidential. You must not share your password with anyone.Linked WebsitesWe are not responsible for the content or reliability of linked websites. Listing should not be taken as endorsement of any kind. We cannot guarantee that these links will work all of the time and we have no control over availability of pages. Furthermore, we are not responsible for the privacy & Data Protection policies and practices of other websites, even if you accessed the third party website using links from our website. We recommend that you check the policy of each website you visit and contact the operator of such website if you have concerns or questions.CookiesCookies are pieces of data transferred to your computer’s hard disk from a website. Each cookie contains a unique, anonymous number. They are stored in the cookie directory of your hard drive, and do not expire at the end of your web browsing session. Cookies allow our website to store data about your browsing patterns, making the website more useful to you. They are very common and are found throughout the internet. Each time you use our website, the cookie is accessed. This allows us to track the features you use and the pages and content that you view on our website. The data obtained by the cookies may be used for analysis and statistical purposes, as well as to help personalise your experience via tailored ads on social media and on other websites. Cookies used by the company contain no personal data about the customer. Most browsers are automatically configured to accept cookies. However, cookies on each website may be safely turned off by customers, without affecting how pages are displayed. Intellectual PropertyAll rights are reserved, including copyright and database rights. Our website and the information contained within them, is protected by copyright. The names, images, pictures and logos identifying the company are proprietary marks of Bob Millar Limited (T/A Auchterlonies of St Andrews). Copying our logos and/or any other third party logos accessed via our website is not permitted without prior approval from us. Reproduction of part or all of the website’ contents in any form is prohibited unless for personal use. Content of our website may not be edited, altered, adapted in any way or copied to any other publication (including electronic, hard copy or others). Interior deep linking or framing of our website is prohibited without the prior consent of the company.Terms and ConditionsOther terms and conditions may also apply for a specific service offered by the company. You shall be subject to any such additional terms and conditions, in addition to your agreement to the terms of this Privacy & Data Protection Policy.JurisdictionThis Privacy & Data Protection Policy and any litigation arising from it shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of Scotland. Any dispute arising under these terms and conditions shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the Scots courts.   Free DeliveryFast and free shipping onUK orders over £75Great ServiceCall us on +44 (0) 1334 473 253for expert, personal adviceSecure PaymentAll major debit and credit cardsaccepted, including Paypal Copyright © 2020 Auchterlonies | Address: Golf Place, St Andrews, KY16 9JA | Telephone: +44(0)1334 473253 | Email: sales@auchterlonies.com | Web
